I'm a soldier, znatchit ya...
I'm a soldier, and that means...
...i otvetchik i sud'ya
...that I am both defendant and judge.
Ya stoyu na dvuh kontsah ognya
I stand at both ends of the fire.
Ogibaya virazhi,
Leaning into the curves,
obgonyaya smert' i zhizn',
overtaking life and death,
ya begu srazit'sya s ten'yu lzhi
I'm running to fight the shadow of lies.
Skol'ko b nitej ne plyol obman,
No matter how tangled the web of deception is woven,
pokazhet lik sveta istina...
truth will always illuminate the outline of the light...
Save your tears for the day...
...when the pain is far behind.
On your feet, come with me.
We are soldiers, stand or die.
Save your fears, take your place.
Save them for the Judgment Day.
Fast and free, follow me.
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall...
Finding out a galaxy...
...of planets and stars within me...
Listening to each of them...
...singing the same silent melody...
I've never seen such beauty...
In possibility...
No speck of doubt or fear...
Wake up!
I hear a voice,
hear a voice calling out to me...
I see inside,
see the light now ever holding me...
All the truth, all I need...
...to make of this reality, it's inside...
The beauty within the shell...
I hear a voice,
hear a voice calling out to me...
I see inside,
see the light now ever holding me...
All the truth, all I need...
...to make of this reality, it's inside...
Right here within the shell...